

+44 7903 809381 hello@karabeen.com

www.karabeen.com www.linkedin.com/in/karabeen

Newcastle-upon-Tyne United Kingdom

# Svyatoslav Polishchuk

**Product Designer** 

#### **PROFILE**

A final year Interactive Design student at Northumbria University with strong skills in problem-solving, UI design, UX design, UX research as well as applying user-centred design principles and methodologies. Has more than 3-year experience in UI/UX field working within agencies and product teams developing solutions for complex business, social and technical challenges.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **UX Designer**

MAY 2017 - AUG 2017

SoPost (Newcastle upon Tyne, UK)

Being a member of a platform team, designed, prototyped and built user interface of internal microservices using HTML and CSS which improved sales team efficiency. Additionally, made all internal user interfaces consistent by developing and implementing custom Bootstrap theme.

### Senior UX/UI and Visual Designer

JUL 2016 - SEP 2016

Binary Studio (Lviv, Ukraine)

During summer break, worked for a software development agency and was responsible for leading all brand creative including prototypes and designs of internal projects, landing pages, emails and events promoting materials.

## **UX/UI Designer**

JUL 2014 - SEP 2015

Happy Design (Lviv, Ukraine)

Being a part of one of the leading local design studios, worked closely with executive team members of key clients to identified, designed and implemented interfaces for various web, mobile and cross-platform applications in Social Network, e-Commerce and Instant Messaging fields.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Northumbria University**

2015 - Current

BA, Interactive Media Design

# Lviv Polytechnic National University

2014 - 2016

MArch, Urban Planning

# Lviv Polytechnic National University

2010 - 2014

BArch, Architecture

#### SKILL SET

Product Design, Interaction Design, UI Design, UX Design, UX Research, Market Research, Concept Modelling, Information Architecture, Strategy Development, Storyboarding, Wireframing, Physical Computing, Prototyping, Usability Testing

Adobe Creative Suite, Sketch, Principle, InVision, Zeplin HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, WordPress